A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Rare Books Dept. Correspondence (miscellaneous)
    - Book Binding (see also Binding) (Box A35-14L)
    - Book catalogues handling (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Collectors (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Collectors Virginia (Box A35-14L)
    - Book dealers - special announcements (Box A35-14L)
    - Book distributors (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Evaluation (see also Appraisals, Book Appraisals) (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Labels (see also Bookplates) (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Lists (Box A35-14L)
    - Book Orders (Box A35-14L)
    - Bookplates (see also Book Labels) (Box A35-14M)
    - Book Prices (Box A35-14M)
    - Booksellers - auction (Box A35-14M)
    - Booksellers - foreign (Box A35-14M)
    - Books, State Appropriations for (Box A35-14M)
    - Borges, Jorge Luis (Box A35-14M)
    - Boston Athenaeum (Box A35-14M)
    - Boston Public Library (Box A35-14M)
    - Botts, John Minor (Box A35-14M)
    - Boulware, Hodge C. (Box A35-14M)
    - Bouvier & Co. (Box A35-14M)
    - Bowdoin College Library (see also Richard Harwell) (Box A35-14M)
    - Bowen, Lem W. (Box A35-14M)
    - Bowers, Fredson (Box A35-14M)
    - Bowers, Nancy Hale (Box A35-14M)
    - Boyd, Julian P. (Box A35-14M)
    - Bradley, Henry T. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brawley, Francis Poe (Box A35-14M)
    - Brecht, Bertolt (Box A35-14M)
    - Brett-Smith, John (Box A35-14M)
    - Brewer, Mrs. Frances J. (see also James B. Cabell) (Box A35-14M)
    - Bricken, Ms. Carl (Box A35-14M)
    - Bridgewater, Dorothy W. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brigham, Clarence (Box A35-14M)
    - Bristol, Roger (Box A35-14M)
    - Broadsides - Southern (Box A35-14M)
    - Brochure - Motley (Box A35-14M)
    - Brodsky, L.D. (Box A35-14M)
    - Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar (Box A35-14M)
    - Brong, Ruth E. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brooks, Cleanth (Box A35-14M)
    - University of Virginia Brooks Museum (Box A35-14M)
    - Brooks, Mrs. Edwin B., Jr (Box A35-14M)
    - Brooks, Mrs. Nelson M. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, Charles B. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, H.B. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, John (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, Joseph E. (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, Lloyd (Box A35-14M)
    - Brown, John Carter, Library (Box A35-14N)
    - Brown, M.L. (Box A35-14N)
    - Brown, Mary C. (Box A35-14N)
    - Brown, Stuart E., Jr. (Box A35-14N)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew (Box A35-14N)
    - Brydon, Anne P. (Box A35-14N)
    - Budget - Annual & Biennial Request (Box A35-14N)
    - Buhler, Curt (Box A35-14N)
    - Bull, Jacqueline (Box A35-14N)
    - The Bur Press (Box A35-14N)
    - Burke, P. Declan (Box A35-14N)
    - Burnham, Jean (Box A35-14N)
    - Burns, Robert (Box A35-14N)
    - Burns, Vincent Godfrey (Box A35-14N)
    - University of Virginia Bursar (Box A35-14N)
    - Butt, Mrs. C.H. (Elizabeth) (Box A35-14N)
    - Bynner (see also Roger E. Stoddard) (Box A35-14N)
    - Byrd, Mason S. (Box A35-14N)
    - Byrd, Ruth Evelyn (Box A35-14N)
    - Byrd, William, I. (Box A35-14N)
    - William Byrd Press (Box A35-14N)
    - Byrer, Frederick O. (Box A35-14N)
    - Cataloguing (1956 - ) (Box A35-14N)
    - C General 1956-1986 (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell, James B. (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell, James Branch - bibliography (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell, James Branch - correspondence 1957-1961 (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell Family (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell, Mrs. J.B. (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabell, Robert G. (Box A35-14O)
    - Cabet, Etienne (Box A35-14O)
    - Cadle, Dean (Box A35-14O)
    - Cadmus Book Shop (Box A3514O-)
    - Cady, Lydston David B. (Box A35-14O)
    - Cahoon, Herbert (Box A35-14O)
    - Cahoun, Herbert (Box A35-14O)
    - The Champlain Society (Box A35-14P)
    - Cabell - speech given by Mr. Runge 1965 June meeting (Box A35-14P)
    - Caldwell, Erskine (Box A35-14P)
    - Caldwell, Erskine - "God's Little Acre" (Box A35-14P)
    - Caldwell Exhibit (Box A35-14P)
    - Calendar for finding dates past & future (Box A35-14P)
    - Calhoun, John T. (Box A35-14P)
    - Calhoun, Philo C. (Box A35-14P)
    - California (Box A35-14P)
    - California Antiquarian (Box A35-14P)
    - California Book Auction Co. (Box A35-14P)
    - California Historical Society (Box A35-14P)
    - University of California - correspondence (Box A35-14P)
    - California, Univ. of - library (Box A35-)
    - Cambridge Bibliographical Society (Box A35-14P)
    - Campbell, Thomas (Box A35-14P)
    - Canaday, John E. (Box A35-14P)
    - Canfield Paper Company (Box A35-14P)
    - Caperton, Bernard (Box A35-14P)
    - Capital Outlay requests (Box A35-14P)
    - Capitation lists (Box A35-14P)
    - Capon Springs (Box A35-14P)
    - Cappon, Lester J. (Box A35-14P)
    - Cards, letters, misc. notes (Box A35-14P)
    - Carpenter, Edwin H., Jr. (Box A35-14P)
    - Carpenter, Margaret (Box A35-14P)
    - Carr's Hill (Box A35-14P)
    - Carroll, George (Box A35-14P)
    - Carroll, Gordon (Box A35-14P)
    - Carter, Mrs. Barbara Nye (Box A35-14P)
    - Carter, John (British Embassy) (Box A35-14P)
    - "Chapter & Verse" - acknowledgements (Box A35-14Q)
    - Carter, William A. (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cartoons (Box A35-14Q)
    - Carver, Marjorie (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cassell, C.F. (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cassell, Clair F. (Box A35-14Q)
    - Catalogues (Box A35-14Q)
    - Catalogues - books (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cataloguing statistics (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cataloguing (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cataloguing Project (Box A35-14Q)
    - Cataloging - Online Catalog Planning Committee (Box A35-14R)
    - Catesby (Box A35-14R)
    - Cather, Willa (Box A35-14R)
    - Catlin, Avery (Box A35-14R)
    - Catlin, Randolph (Box A35-14R)
    - Cauthen, Irby B. (Box A35-14R)
    - Cave family (Box A35-14R)
    - Cauthen, Irby B., Jr. (Box A35-14R)
    - Cazemajou, J. (Box A35-14R)
    - CBS program on Jefferson and Monticello (Box A35-14R)
    - Cecil, Mrs. H.I. (Box A35-14R)
    - Century Association (Box A35-14R)
    - Ceylon (Box A35-14R)
    - Chaloner (Box A35-14R)
    - Chamberlain, B.P. (Box A35-14R)
    - Champney, James Wells (Box A35-14R)
    - Chapin Library (see also Williams College) (Box A35-14R)
    - Chapman (Box A35-14R)
    - Chapman, John Gadsby (Box A35-14R)
    - Chappell, Warren (Box A35-14R)
    - Chappell, Warren (Box A35-14S)
    - Charlottesville - history (Box A35-14S)
    - Charlottesville General Hospital (Box A35-14S)
    - Charvat, William (Box A35-14S)
    - Chaves (Box A35-14S)
    - Chesterfield County (Box A35-14S)
    - Chew Family Papers (Box A35-14S)
    - Childs, J. Rives (Box A35-14S)
    - Chile (Box A35-14S)
    - Chiswick Book Shop (Box A35-14S)
    - Christian Science (Box A35-14S)
    - Christie, Manson & Woods, Ltd. (Box A35-14S)
    - Churchill, Charles - "Poems" (Box A35-14S)
    - Churchill, Winston (Box A35-14S)
    - Circulation (Box A35-14S)
    - Monthly Circulation Reports 1972 July - 1977 June (Box A35-14S)
    - Civil War Centennial (Box A35-14T)
    - Civil War session broadsides (Box A35-14T)
    - Civil War recordings (Box A35-14T)
    - The Arthur H. Clark Company (Box A35-14T)
    - Clark, Barrett H. collection (Box A35-14T)
    - Clark, Josephine Glasgow (Box A35-14T)
    - Clarke, Marian (Box A35-14T)
    - Clark's Travels in the Old South (Box A35-14T)
    - Classified Statements (Box A35-14T)
    - Claytor, William G., Jr. (Box A35-14T)
    - Cleaning schedule (Box A35-14T)
    - Cleland, Thomas M. (Box A35-14T)
    - Clemens, Samuel (Box A35-14T)
    - Clements Library (Box A35-14T)
    - Clinch, Mrs. Frances H.B. (Box A35-14T)
    - Clinch Valley College (Box A35-14T)
    - Closeup sheets (Box A35-14T)
    - Cloture rule (Box A35-14T)
    - Cobb, Carl B. (Box A35-14T)
    - Cochran, Louis (Box A35-14T)
    - Coffin, Stanley (Box A35-14T)
    - J.J. Cohane (Box A35-14T)
    - Cohn, Mrs. Louis Henry (Box A35-14T)
    - Coke, William Hardie (Box A35-14T)
    - Cokesbury Book Store (Box A35-14T)
    - Cole, Redmond S. (Box A35-14T)
    - Coleman, Mrs. Elinor W. (Box A35-14T)
    - Coles, Edward (Box A35-14T)
    - Coles Fund (Box A35-14T)
    - Colker, Marvin L. (Box A35-14T)
    - Collections - Literary (Box A35-15A)
    - Collectors -Civil War (Box A35-15A)
    - Collectors - Private (Box A35-15A)
    - College & Research Libraries (Box A35-15A)
    - Collier's Encyclopedia (Box A35-15A)
    - University of Virginia Colonnade Club (Box A35-15A)
    - Colonial Williamsburg (Box A35-15A)
    - Colt, Harris D. (Box A35-15A)
    - Cometti, Elizabeth (1956- ) (Box A35-15A)
    - University of Virginia Committee on Special Lectures (Box A35-15A)
    - Community Chest (Box A35-15A)
    - Comparator Research Associates (Box A35-15A)
    - Confederate Newspapers (Box A35-15A)
    - Conferences (Box A35-15A)
    - Conference of Early American History (Box A35-15A)
    - Conkwright, P.F. (typographer) (Box A35-15A)
    - Conovich, Mrs. Lucille D. (Box A35-15A)
    - Conway, Mrs. Carl C. (Box A35-15A)
    - Cook, Capt. James (Box A35-15A)
    - Cookbooks (Box A35-15A)
    - Cooke, John Esten (Box A35-15A)
    - Cooper, Fred B. (Box A35-15A)
    - Cooper, James Fenimore (Box A35-15A)
    - Cooper, Weldon (Box A35-15A)
    - Copyright - Registration (Box A35-15A)
    - Cornell University (Box A35-15A)
    - Correspondence (Box A35-15A)
    - Correspondence (1974 Sept. - ) (Box A35-15A)
    - Courtenay (Box A35-15B)
    - Cowen, Mrs. W. Walker (Juliette) (Box A35-15B)
    - Cowgill, Logan O. (Box A35-15B)
    - Cowper (Box A35-15B)
    - Coxe, Daniel (Box A35-15B)
    - Coyle, George S. (Box A35-15B)
    - Coyner, Boyd (Box A35-15B)
    - Craig, Archibald (see also Cumming, W.P.) (Box A35-15B)
    - Craig, Fannie (Box A35-15B)
    - Crane, Stephen (Box A35-15B)
    - Crawford, Richard (Box A35-15B)
    - Cremin, Robert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A35-15B)
    - Critics, Janet (Box A35-15B)
    - Crittenden, C.C. (Box A35-15B)
    - Crusoe, Robinson (Box A35-15B)
    - Cumming, Hugh S., Jr. (Box A35-15B)
    - Cumming - West (gift) (Box A35-15B)
    - Cumming, W.P. (see also Archibald Craig) (Box A35-15B)
    - (Box A35-15B)
    - Cundall, Joseph (see also Publishing) (Box A35-15B)
    - Curtis Paper Co. (Box A35-15B)
    - Curzan, Mary (Box A35-15B)
    - Cushing, John D. (Box A35-15B)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box A35-15B)
    - D - General (Box A35-15C)
    - Dabney, Douglas H. (Box A35-15C)
    - Dabney, Virginius (Box A35-15C)
    - Daedalus Bookshop / McAdams, Sandy (Box A35-15C)
    - D'Alfonce, J.E. (Box A35-15C)
    - Dallas Public Library (see also Turner, Decherd) (Box A35-15C)
    - Dalton, Jack (Box A35-15C)
    - Daniel, Mr. & Mrs. Robert (Box A35-15C)
    - Daniel, Price, Jr. (Box A35-15C)
    - Daniels, Alice C. (Box A35-15C)
    - Dante (Box A35-15C)
    - Danton, J. Periam (Box A35-15C)
    - Danville Virginia (Box A35-15C)
    - Dartmouth Library, Friends of (Box A35-15C)
    - Dartt, R.L. (Box A35-15C)
    - Darwin Collection (Box A35-15C)
    - Davenport, Braxton (Box A35-15C)
    - Daub, Albert W. (Box A35-15C)
    - Davidson, Alexander, Jr. (Box A35-15C)
    - Davis, Curtis C. (Box A35-15C)
    - Davis, Lambert (Box A35-15C)
    - Davis, Richard Beale (Box A35-15C)
    - Davison, Charles M., Jr. (Box A35-15C)
    - Davison, J.F.M. (Box A35-15C)
    - Dawson, Damon (Box A35-15C)
    - Day, A. Grove (Box A35-15C)
    - Day, W. Chilton (Box A35-15C)
    - Deal, Harvey (Box A35-15C)
    - Duplicates - credit with dealers (Box A35-15D)
    - Declaration 1620 (Box A35-15D)
    - Declaration of Independence (Box A35-15D)
    - DeGraffenreid Fund Account 8081 (Box A35-15D)
    - Dekker (Box A35-15D)
    - Delauney, Clay (Box A35-15D)
    - Historical Society of Delaware (Box A35-15D)
    - Denmark (Box A35-15D)
    - Denny, Collins (Box A35-15D)
    - De Pauw University (Box A35-15D)
    - Deposits (Box A35-15D)
    - Deposits Rare Books (1961 - ) (Box A35-15D)
    - Detective Stories (Box A35-15D)
    - Detroit Public Library (Box A35-15D)
    - University of Virginia Development Office (Box A35-15D)
    - Devonshire (Box A35-15D)
    - Dewey News Sheet (Box A35-15D)
    - Dichter, Harry (Box A35-15D)
    - Dickens, Charles (Box A35-15D)
    - Dickinson, Emily (Box A35-15D)
    - Dickinson, Josiah L. (Box A35-15D)
    - Dickson, Sarah (Box A35-15D)
    - Dictionaries (Box A35-15D)
    - Diderot (Box A35-15D)
    - Dierkes, Henry (Box A35-15D)
    - Dillard, Hardy C. (Box A35-15D)
    - Dillon, Virginia H. (see also Lottie J. Hinton) (Box A35-15D)
    - Dime Novel (Box A35-15D)
    - Dimick, Mr. and Mrs. John (Box A35-15D)
    - University of Virginia Library Directors' Council (Box A35-15D)
    - University of Virginia Library Directors' Council - Minutes (Box A35-15D)
    - University of Virginia Library Directors' Council Meetings / Minutes 1970-1983 (Box A35-15E)
    - Displays (Box A35-15E)
    - Display Cases in RBR & MSS (Box A35-15E)
    - Dix, William (Box A35-15E)
    - Documents (Box A35-15E)
    - Documents Collection (Box A35-15E)
    - Document Delivery (Box A35-15E)
    - Doncker, Hendrik (Box A35-15E)
    - R.R. Donnelley & Sons (Box A35-15E)
    - Donor - Prospective (Box A35-15E)
    - Donson, Theodore E. (Box A35-15E)
    - Dorsey, John M. (1956- ) (Box A35-15F)
    - Dos Passos, Elizabeth (Mrs. John Dos Passos) (Box A35-15F)
    - Douglas, George B., III (Box A35-15F)
    - Douglas, William (Box A35-15F)
    - Dow, Douglas (Box A35-15F)
    - Drake Hotel (Box A35-15F)
    - Drake, Mrs. John B. (Box A35-15F)
    - Drayton (see also Jensen) (Box A35-15F)
    - Dreiser, Theodore (Box A35-15F)
    - Drenner, Don (Box A35-15F)
    - Drijver, Corn. (Box A35-15F)
    - Du Fault, Peter Kane (Box A35-15F)
    - Duke, Helen (Box A35-15F)
    - Duke, Mrs. Cammann C. (Box A35-15F)
    - Duke University Library (Box A35-15F)
    - Dulaney, Mrs. Robert (Box A35-15F)
    - Dumas, D. Warner (Box A35-15F)
    - Dunbar, Gary S. (Box A35-15F)
    - Duncan, Andrew (see also George Washington Library Room) (Box A35-15F)
    - Dunglison-Dorsey Publication / notes by Mr. Runge (Box A35-15F)
    - Dunn, James C. (Box A35-15F)
    - Duplicates Sold (Box A35-15F)
    - Durell, Edward (Box A35-15F)
    - Dust Jackets (Box A35-15F)
    - Dwyer, Mr. & Mrs. Charles A. (Box A35-15F)
    - E - General 1957-1986 (Box A35-15G)
    - Eager, George B. (Box A35-15G)
    - Early American Imprints / Shaw-Shoemaker (Box A35-15G)
    - Early American Imprints (Box A35-15G)
    - Eastern Airlines (Box A35-15G)
    - George Eastman House (Box A35-15G)
    - Easton, Mrs. Ralph O. (Box A35-15G)
    - Eberstadt, Charles (Box A35-15G)
    - Eberstadt, Edward, & Sons (Box A35-15G)
    - Echols, Robert (Box A35-15G)
    - Edel, Leon (Box A35-15G)
    - Edelstein, J.M. (Box A35-15G)
    - Edgerton, Mr. & Mrs. Milton T., Jr. (Box A35-15G)
    - Edinburgh Bibliographical Society (Box A35-15G)
    - Educational & Employment Opportunities / Shannon, David (Box A35-15G)
    - Edwards, Lillian Perry (Box A35-15G)
    - Einstein, Albert (Box A35-15G)
    - Eisel, Paul J. (Box A35-15G)
    - Election Sermons (Box A35-15G)
    - Eliot-Schwab Collection (Box A35-15G)
    - Elliott, John Page (Box A35-15G)
    - Ellis, T.K. (Box A35-15G)
    - Emergency Procedures (Box A35-15G)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Box A35-15G)
    - Emory University Library (Box A35-15H)
    - Employment (Box A35-15H)
    - Employment and Termination Date of Employees (Box A35-15H)
    - Encyclopedia of Library and Information Science (Box A35-15H)
    - Eneas Africanus (Box A35-15H)
    - Energy Conservation Committee (Box A35-15H)
    - English Books - 16th Century (Box A35-15H)
    - English Club (Box A35-15H)
    - English Pilot (Box A35-15H)
    - Engraving (Box A35-15H)
    - Equal Opportunity (Box A35-15H)
    - Equipment and Maintenance (Box A35-15H)
    - Equipment (Box A35-15H)
    - Equipment Requests (Box A35-15H)
    - Erasmus Press Publications (Box A35-15H)
    - Erskine, Albert (Box A35-15H)
    - Etherington, Donald (Box A35-15H)
    - Evangliar Des Rabbula (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans, Charles (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans, William F. (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans Index - Bristol (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans Addenda (Box A35-15H)
    - "Evans - Not In" (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans Supplements - Bristol (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans - Sabin Microcard Corp. 1957 (Box A35-15H)
    - Evans-Sabin Microcard Project (Box A35-15I)
    - Evans-Sabin Catalog Cards (Box A35-15I)
    - Evans-Sabin Microcard Project - Graham (Box A35-15I)
    - Evans-Sabin Microcard Project - Microcard Corp. correspondence 1956 (Box A35-15I)
    - Events, Special (Box A35-15I)
    - Evergreen House (Box A35-15I)
    - Ewald, Mrs. & Mrs. John A., Jr. (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibit Cards (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibit - correspondence (1956 - ) (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibition Catalogues - "American Writer in England" (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibition Catalogue -mailing list (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibits (with photographs) (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibits - Medical (Box A35-15I)
    - Exhibits (Box A35-15J)
    - Alford, Neill H., Jr. - exhibition held in the Law Library (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Afro-American (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Architecture - Wiebenson (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Bicentennial - Jefferson's Fine Arts Library (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition -The Book Art (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Fredson Bowers (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Lewis Carroll (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Willa Cather (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Warren Chappell - "Fifty Years of Graphic Work" (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Color-plate books (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Diderot's Encyclopedia (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Dugdale, Sir William (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Early American Book Illustrators and Wood Engravers (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Early Kentuckiana (Box A35-15J)
    - Early Virginia Libraries Traveling Exhibition (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - The English Avant-Garde of the 1880's ... (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - William Faulkner (Box A35-15J)
    - Exhibition - Formerly in the possession of ... (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - From Palm to Pine (Kipling) (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Robert Frost (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The Fugitives (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Gothic Novel - Sadleir-Black (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - "The Grand Tour and Beyond" (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Lafcadio Hearn (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Ernest Hemingway (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - the Illustrated London News (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Mackay-Smith (music) (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The Madisons of Montpelier (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - "Maps of Virginia" (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Cotton Mather (Box A35-15K)
    - Tracy W. McGregor - His Library of Americana (includes John Forbes exhibit) (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Naturalis Historia (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The New World (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Palladio (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - John Dos Passos (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Recent Acquisitions (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Revolutionary America 1763-1783 (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Romantic Literature (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Marion duPont Scott (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The Sitwells (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The Spell of Italy: British & American Travel Accounts 1800-1914 (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Thomas Jefferson: His Times and his Contemporaries (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - "Treasures of Learning" Keystones of the Barrett Library (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - The Virginia Author (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - George Washington (Box A35-15K)
    - Exhibition - Frank Lloyd Wright (Box A35-15K)
    - F- General (Box A35-15L)
    - Facsimiles (Box A35-15L)
    - [University of Virginia] Faculty of Arts & Sciences - agenda 1967-1971 (Box A35-15L)
    - [University of Virginia] Faculty - Leave Policy & Meetings & Misc. (Box A35-15M)
    - [University of Virginia] Faculty Performance Evaluations (Box A35-15M)
    - [University of Virginia] Faculty Salary Increases (Box A35-15M)
    - Floor Plans (Alderman Library) (Box A35-15M)
    - University of Virginia Faculty Senate (Box A35-15M)
    - Fairburn, J.S. (Box A35-15M)
    - Fairfax, Orlando D. (Box A35-15M)
    - Farmington Country Club (Box A35-15M)
    - Faulkner Catalogue 1968 (Box A35-15M)
    - Faulkner Fund (Box A35-15M)
    - Faulkner, William (Box A35-15M)
    - Faulkner, William - building (see also Old Ivy Inn) (Box A35-15M)
    - Fauntleroy (Box A35-15M)
    - Fawcett, John - collections (Box A35-15M)
    - Federal Aid to Education (Box A35-15M)
    - Federal Programs of Library Assistance (Box A35-15M)
    - Feet Bare (Box A35-15M)
    - Feger, Mildred Weaver (Box A35-15M)
    - Feinberg, Charles E. (Box A35-15M)
    - Fencing / duelling (Box A35-15M)
    - Ferguson, W. Craig (Box A35-15M)
    - Files - Inactive (Box A35-15M)
    - Finding Aids / VCRP (Virginia Colonial Records Project) (Box A35-15N)
    - Finestone, Harry (Box A35-15N)
    - Finland (Box A35-15N)
    - Fire extinguishers (Box A35-15N)
    - Firmage, George J. (Box A35-15N)
    - Fiske Kimball Library (Box A35-15N)
    - Fitzgerald Newsletter 1961 (Box A35-15N)
    - Fitzhugh, George (Box A35-15N)
    - Fitzhugh, Stuart & Donald (Box A35-15N)
    - Fleming, John F. (Box A35-15N)
    - Fleming, Thomas H. (Box A35-15N)
    - University of Florida (Box A35-15N)
    - Fluvanna County Historical Society (Box A35-15N)
    - Folger Shakespeare Library (Box A35-15N)
    - Forbes Papers (Box A35-15N)
    - Ford, Alice (Box A35-15N)
    - Foreign Languages (Box A35-15N)
    - Forestry Rare Books (Box A35-15N)
    - Form Letter - Inquiries about orders (Box A35-15N)
    - Former Employees (Box A35-15N)
    - Foss, Edward (Box A35-15N)
    - Foundation Library Center (Box A35-15N)
    - [University of Virginia] Founder's Day (Box A35-15N)
    - Fox, John R. (Box A35-15N)
    - Foxing (Box A35-15N)
    - Frantz, Ray W., Jr. (Box A35-15N)
    - Fraser, Ian Forbes (Box A35-15O)
    - Free Library, Friends of (Box A35-15O)
    - Freeman, Samuel T. and Co. (Box A35-15O)
    - Freemasons (Box A35-15O)
    - French, Bryant (Box A35-15O)
    - French, Hannah (Box A35-15O)
    - French, Mrs. Hannah D. (Box A35-15O)
    - Friedman, Ira J. (Box A35-15O)
    - Friends of Aberdeen University Library (Box A35-15O)
    - Frost, Robert - Exhibit (Box A35-15O)
    - Frost, Robert - Chicago Exhibit 1962 Nov (Box A35-15O)
    - Frost, Robert - requests for catalogue (Box A35-15O)
    - Frost, Robert - "Twilight" (Box A35-15O)
    - Fry-Jefferson map (Box A35-15O)
    - Fugate, Mary C. (Box A35-15O)
    - G - General (Box A35-15P)
    - Gaines, Pierce (Box A35-15P)
    - Galban, Mrs. Julio Suarez (Box A35-15P)
    - Gallup, Donald (Box A35-15P)
    - Galsworthy, John (Box A35-15P)
    - Gamble, Edward (Box A35-15P)
    - Gamble, Mrs. Edward W. (Box A35-15P)
    - Gammans, Harold W. (Box A35-15P)
    - Gannon, Thomas J., Inc. (Box A35-15P)
    - Ganter, Herbert (Box A35-15P)
    - Garbee, Robert H. (Box A35-15P)
    - Garlick, R.C. (Box A35-15P)
    - The Garnetts of Elmwood (Box A35-15P)
    - Garruto, John (Box A35-15P)
    - Gass, Edmund C. (Box A35-15P)
    - Gates, William C. (Box A35-15P)
    - Gawthrop, Margaret D. (Box A35-15P)
    - Generall Historie (Box A35-15P)
    - Geoffrey, Leon S. (Box A35-15P)
    - George Mason University (Box A35-15P)
    - Georgia (Box A35-15P)
    - German, Germans, Germany (Box A35-15P)
    - Gerritsen, Johan (Box A35-15P)
    - Gertz, Elmer (see also Henry Miller) (Box A35-15P)
    - Gifts - Policy (Box A35-15P)
    - Gifts - Tax deductions (Box A35-15P)
    - Gilliam, Franklin (Box A35-15P)
    - Gilmer, Mr. & Mrs. George (Box A35-15P)
    - Giniger, Kenneth S. (Box A35-15P)
    - Ginsberg, Louis (Box A35-15Q)
    - Girl Scouts (Box A35-15Q)
    - Glasgow University (Box A35-15Q)